(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Well, then, uh,
first things first.
(Sheldon:)Um, are you familiar with
the Brachistochrone problem?
(Amy:)I am.
Good.
(Sheldon:)And how it relates
to the calculus of variations?
(Howard:)It's an inverted cycloid.
(Sheldon:)Wonderful.
(Sheldon:)Now, what about
Euler-Lagrange theorems?
(Howard:)That's where I'm a little fuzzy.
Ha! I knew it! All right.
(Sheldon:)We have a lot of information
to cover before your first test.
(Sheldon:)Which, by the way,
is in eight minutes.
(Sheldon:)The good news is I'm
grading on a curve,
(Sheldon:)so you're pretty much
guaranteed a C.
♪ All I do is win, win, win ♪
♪ No matter what ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Everybody hands go up, up... ♪
♪ And they stay there! ♪
(Sheldon:)What are you doing?
(Howard:)If you're gonna be
a crappy teacher,
(Howard:)then I'm gonna be
a crappy student.
(grunts) ♪ Ludacris going in
on the verse ♪
♪ 'Cause I never been defeated
and I won't stop now... ♪
Will you stop it!
(Sheldon:)This is a classroom.
This is not American Bandstand.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Now, where was I?
(Sheldon:)Let's see.